<resources>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="content_shopping_guide_caution"><![CDATA[<font color=#B00020>※</font><font color=#000000> The estimated price of Korean won is converted to US $ 1.00 = KW1,200, which is different from the amount actually paid overseas. Duties / tax may be added depending on the type and price of overseas goods purchased. Please check today\'s exchange rate information before purchase.Also, AllLink Share fastballs are not directly involved in overseas products.</font><br/><br/><font color=#B00020>※</font><font color=#000000> Als Shopping only provides the product information received from each shopping mall, so it may not match the information of the shopping mall, so please check the correct information at the shopping mall. View Legal Notice below</font><br/><br/>Precautions for Cash Payment: Please make sure to use escrow payment to ensure transaction safety when making cash payments such as unpaid accounts.<br/><br/><font color=#B00020>Limitation of Liability and Legal Notice</font><font color="#000000"><br/><br/>1.Als shopping service collects and organizes information (commodity information, price information, product composition, images, etc.) of the Internet shopping malls open on the Internet for the convenience of Internet shopping users, helping them to conveniently compare and purchase products. Service.<br/><br/>2.Linkshare Co., Ltd. endeavors to provide accurate or reliable information about the information distributed, transmitted and exposed through Als Shopping, including links, downloads, and advertisements within Als Shopping, but may occur in the process. No warranty is made as to the accuracy or reliability of the information and no liability is assumed for any direct, indirect, consequential, punitive or incidental damages arising from the error of the information. In addition, it is solely the user\'s responsibility to trust the information provided by Als Shopping (product information, price information, form composition, image, etc.), and the user must check the product color, size, and detailed product composition at the shopping mall. The duty and responsibility of ordering, shipping and refunding the goods lies with the mall.<br/><br/>3.All shopping malls in Als Shopping are independently owned and operated by the shopping malls, and are fully responsible for the shopping malls. Linkshare Co., Ltd. expressly assumes any responsibility for transactions between the user and the shopping mall, such as any activities, shopping, goods or services provided in the shopping mall, or contents posted, or any damage, loss or injury resulting from access or inability to access the shopping mall. No obligation or obligation. If you have any questions or complaints about various products or services offered by the shopping mall, please contact the shopping mall directly. Every shopping mall homepage has a link to provide contact information. Effective Date: January 1, 2020<br/><br/></font><font color=#B00020>Notes on Cash Payment</font><font color=#000000><br/><br/>Als Shopping goes through rigorous screening to comply with all relevant laws and regulations, including the `` Act on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce, \'\' etc. when entering a shopping mall. In addition, we strive to provide high-quality information to our users by regularly monitoring and checking whether payment methods work properly. However, if a certain shopping mall is planning a fraudulent behavior after entering the store, there is a limit to preventing all of this beforehand, so users also need to be careful. In particular, it is typical of fraudulent shopping malls to induce cash payments due to temptations such as discounts, and do not deliver goods. In order to prevent such fraud, please use escrow payment when depositing cash.<br/><br/>1.  Representative cash induction in fraudulent shopping malls<br/>  - Cash discount event (e.g. new member\'s cash discount coupon, etc.)<br/>  - No card payments, induction of unpaid passbook without escrow<br/>  - Make a phone call after paying for the card, and induce the transfer of funds by using the bait ‘additional discount, etc.’<br/>  - Too cheap to sell at other shopping malls<br/><br/>2.  Prevention of Fraud<br/>  - Credit card payment whenever possible<br/>  - If cash payment is inevitable, check whether the cash payment is applied with escrow service<br/>  - No cash payment without escrow<br/>  - If you make an escrow cash payment, you can get rid of the damage even in a fraudulent shopping mall.<br/><br/>3.  How to check if you have escrow<br/>  - What is Escrow?<br/>  - Escrow is used to ensure the safety of transactions by means of intermediary, trading of money or goods by a trusted neutral third party between the seller and the buyer in e-commerce transactions.<br/><br/>  - How do I tell if my payment is escrowed?<br/>Providers of escrow services are largely divided into banknotes and PG companies.<br/>There may be a slight difference in the way of providing escrow for each business. However, when you select a bank account, the payment information is entered on the escrow pop-up page.<br/><br/>1.Order<br/>2.After the payment is made, the payment button<br/>3.Escrow operator page pop-up<br/>4.Enter the payment information<br/>5.Payment Completed<br/>Escrow Do not go to the general account transfer page without pop-up page, you will not be protected. Please check the details of the escrow provided by each company before making a payment</font>]]></string>
    <string name="content_shopping_guide_customs_tariff"><![CDATA[<font color=#B00020>※</font><font color="#00000"><em> General customs clearance</em><br/><br/>Examination proceeds after directly checking the goods and the customs clearance documents declared to the customs</font><br/><br/><font color="#DF9E26">If the taxable price exceeds 150,000 won, VAT is charged</font><br/><br/><font color=#B00020>※</font><font color="#00000"><em> Customs clearance</em><br/><br/>Customs clearance examination proceeds with the customs clearance documents declared to customs</font><br/><br/><font color="#DF9E26">VAT is charged when the value of the item exceeds $ 200 (tax not included, actual total purchase price)</font>]]></string>
</resources>